{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908746740","data":{"timestamp":" 946908746739"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" d8e18eea-f634-4462-a5c7-71d170631091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908756675","data":{"timestamp":" 946908756675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908757058","data":{"timestamp":" 946908757058"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908757293","data":{"timestamp":" 946908757293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908757610","data":{"timestamp":" 946908757610"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908757844","data":{"timestamp":" 946908757844"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908761298","data":{"timestamp":" 946908761298"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908761593","data":{"timestamp":" 946908761593"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908762506","data":{"timestamp":" 946908762506"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908762931","data":{"timestamp":" 946908762931"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908765849","data":{"timestamp":" 946908765849"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908766134","data":{"timestamp":" 946908766134"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908766978","data":{"timestamp":" 946908766978"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908767644","data":{"timestamp":" 946908767644"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908768380","data":{"timestamp":" 946908768380"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908768710","data":{"timestamp":" 946908768710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908768985","data":{"timestamp":" 946908768985"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908769305","data":{"timestamp":" 946908769304"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908769762","data":{"timestamp":" 946908769761"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908773330","data":{"timestamp":" 946908773330"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908773717","data":{"timestamp":" 946908773717"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908773952","data":{"timestamp":" 946908773952"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908774269","data":{"timestamp":" 946908774269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908774508","data":{"timestamp":" 946908774508"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908778017","data":{"timestamp":" 946908778017"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908778315","data":{"timestamp":" 946908778315"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908779222","data":{"timestamp":" 946908779222"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908779649","data":{"timestamp":" 946908779648"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908782585","data":{"timestamp":" 946908782585"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908782870","data":{"timestamp":" 946908782870"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908783716","data":{"timestamp":" 946908783716"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908784379","data":{"timestamp":" 946908784379"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908785116","data":{"timestamp":" 946908785116"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908785445","data":{"timestamp":" 946908785445"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908785720","data":{"timestamp":" 946908785720"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908786034","data":{"timestamp":" 946908786034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908786306","data":{"timestamp":" 946908786306"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908789842","data":{"timestamp":" 946908789841"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908789995","data":{"timestamp":" 946908789995"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_171212"," gameId":" 6dc7115f-ca8b-4a92-8ac2-cfb05a3f4bb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}